http://www.webundies.com/pages/privacy-policy

Log in
(0)
Item Added to Cart
x
QTY:
Add Gift Message
Please leave your gift message below:
Dr. Seuss
Everything Else!
Dr. Seuss
Everything Else!
Disney
Everything Else!
Dr. Who
Everything Else!
Disney Characters
Everything Else!
Disney Princesses
Everything Else!
Dr. Seuss
Everything Else!
Dr. Seuss
Everything Else!
Disney
Everything Else!
Dr. Who
Everything Else!
Disney Characters
Everything Else!
Disney Princesses
Everything Else!
How We Collect & Use Information
At WebUndies, we firmly believe in your privacy and the security of your personal information. We are committed to using any information you give us in a responsible manner. You're very important to us and we want to provide you with a safe and secure online experience.  We are online shoppers, too, and treat you the way we expect to be treated.
We suggest that you review this privacy statement periodically as we may update it from time to time.  This policy was last updated on 9/8/2020.
What information does WebUndies collect about me?
Every time you visit our website, we collect your Internet service provider's address, the Web page from which you came, and a record of your activity on our site through the use of cookies.  We do not keep this information for any reason- it is only used to aid in your shopping experience. For Google users, Google Analytics will collect Google-authenticated identifiers associated with your Google Accounts and temporarily join these identifiers to support browsing across devices.
When you purchase from WebUndies, we collect information that you volunteer such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number and other information necessary to process your order.
We also collect the information you provide to us when you register for sales notices, participate in a contest or sweepstakes promotion, or sign up for our mailing list.
How do you use my information?
The information we receive allows us to personalize offers and improve your shopping experience, making shopping easier and more enjoyable. It also enables us to process your purchases, confirm your orders, customize the content and layout of our pages, notify you about updates to our websites and products, and provide you with marketing information.
We periodically send you email about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events once you have signed up for our email list. If you do not wish to receive such emails in the future, click the "unsubscribe" link on any promotional email you receive from us. Please note: In order to process your purchases we may send you a confirmation email or we may contact you by mail or telephone if we have questions about your order.
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these agencies or companies for marketing purposes.
What are 'cookies' and how does WebUndies use them?
A "cookie" is a small data file stored on your computer. At WebUndies, we store items added to your shopping cart (so you can come back later and have it waiting), user-specific information on pages accessed, and previous visits to our site in this cookie file.   We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer.
We recognize that you have a choice to refuse cookies. However, by choosing to accept a WebUndies cookie you allow us to store and process your order. If you choose not to accept the cookie, purchasing is not possible on the WebUndies site.
If you are shopping WebUndies and are having difficulty adding product to your shopping cart or completing your order, please check your privacy settings in your browser. If you do not wish to change your privacy settings to "Medium" and you are currently using the "Medium High" or "High" settings, you may choose to override your current cookie handling practices for individual sites that you specify, including WebUndies.com.
How do I know my information is secure?
We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you so you can feel comfortable and secure when shopping. We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving your personal information. On the Internet, when you see either a solid key icon or a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser window, this indicates that the site is secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). Pages requesting personal information should always have one of these icons. Click Here for additional security information.
GDPR and Customer Data
For customers residing in the EU, upon request WebUndies.com will remove order data for that customer from our system.  This includes deleting the order data for the customer or deleting the customer's registered account entirely.  When first visiting WebUndies.com, customers are presented with information on our cookie policy.  By clicking through that notice, you have consented to our data collection practices, as outlined in this policy.
Children's Policy
WebUndies does not seek to solicit information from anyone under the age of thirteen (a "Child"). If a Child submits information to us and we know that the person submitting the information is a Child, we will not use it for any purpose. We will delete the information as soon as we discover it and we will not disclose it to third parties.
Changes To This Privacy Policy Statement
From time to time, we may use the information you provide us for new, unanticipated uses not previously addressed in our Privacy Statement. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes on the privacy page of our website to notify you of these changes. You should check our website periodically for more information on how we use the data we collect.If there is a material change in the manner we use data that we collect, we will update this Privacy Statement to reflect these changes.
Contact Us
Feel free to contact us for any reason, including a request to be added to or taken off a list, or if you have any questions or concerns.WebUndies270 Sheffield Street, Unit BMountainside, NJ 07092help@webundies.com
Please note: When you contact us, please provide your name and e-mail address exactly as it appears on correspondence you have received from us.
All Contents © 2020 by WebUndies.com LLC.
All rights Reserved.
WebUndies.com®, the WebUndies Duck®, and BoxerGram® are all registered trademarks of WebUndies.com LLC
